interviewmagazine.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Interview Magazine

The following constitutes the Privacy Policy adopted by _INTERVIEW_ magazine with respect to its website and any ancillary websites or ancillary services operated by the magazine (collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the "Site").  This Privacy Policy is a part of the Terms of Use that govern your use of the Site.

**Changes**

The Privacy Policy may change from time to time without notice to you. You should read it each time you plan to submit personal information so that you understand how the information you are submitting will be used.  Any changes made to the Privacy Policy will be effective prospectively, and not retroactively.

Although we will endeavor to require third-party content providers and other parties to adhere to our policies, we are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties or for the information practices of any third-party sites to which links may be provided in the Site.

**Collection of Information**

In various ways we collect information that is volunteered by visitors to our site. Certain identifying information, such as name, street address, city, state, zip code and email address, is gathered at certain interactive areas on the site, such as when you subscribe to our print or digital publication while online.  Wherever possible and practical, we give users options about submitting information.

**Subscriptions**

You may subscribe to the print or digital version of _INTERVIEW_ through the Site by following the relevant instructions on the Site.   All subscription-related information is collected on the Site and stored by our fulfillment house.

**Messages and Postings**

We will be free to make use of any message or item posted by you on the Site in any bulletin board or chat room, as set forth in the Terms of Use.   This includes the right to make use of the message or posting in public circumstances or to provide it to any third party.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**

In order to offer and provide personalized custom services, we use cookies to limit the number of times a particular advertisement is shown to a user as the user navigates through the site. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file may contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited and to allow easy access to restricted areas of the website. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk, read cookie files created by other sites, or damage your files.

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You also may refuse cookies by disabling them on your browser.

IP addresses are also recorded in our log files.  We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and similar purposes.

**Use of the Information Collected**

From time to time, we may be approached by third parties with an interest in identifying subscribers to our print or digital publication _._  We may provide them with our publications' mailing list (but not e-mail addresses) if we believe the subscribers in question would be interested in hearing from them.

With respect to advertisements, an advertiser will inform us which type of audience it seeks to reach, and we may place advertisements in the Site that fit the advertiser's criteria.  Pop-up advertisements may be displayed to a targeted audience on the Site based on these criteria. The advertisers are not permitted to access your account or any of your personally identifiable information.

We also use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas.

We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their interests. We do not track the usage patterns of individual users, so an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked on a particular ad.

**Information Sharing**

When you visit the Site and are asked to provide information about yourself, you are sharing that information only with us, unless specifically stated otherwise in this Privacy Policy or as stated in any notice given to you at the time the information was requested.  We will not disclose the information you submit, except as described here in, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure to protect our rights or property, or for administrative or other purposes we deem necessary to maintain or service our products and services. For example, we may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide you with our services.

If you do not want your data to be shared, you may choose not to permit the data to be collected or transferred by not submitting personally identifiable information on our site, or by not using a particular service.

**Security Measures**

The Site has technical and organizational security measures in place, including firewalls, to protect the information under our control from accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure, or access. Such measures do not guarantee prevention of loss, misuse, or alteration of information, however, so while we strive to protect your information, we cannot warrant the security of information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Children's Privacy**

The Site is intended for use by individuals over the age of 16 and not for children. If you are under 16, you should not submit any personally identifiable information on the Site. Children must ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending any personal information online to anyone.

**Other Information About Your Privacy**

You should be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose any information online in any bulletin board or chat room, that information can be collected and used by others. In other words, if you post personal information online that may be accessed by the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or they may use the information in various ways.  It is important to be responsible and careful whenever you are online.

**Updating, Correcting, Deleting or Restricting Personal Information**

If you do not want your personally identifiable information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by letting us know by e-mailing, calling, or writing us. You can also contact us if you wish to review and/or correct your personally identifiable information.

**Contact**

You can contact us with regard to this Privacy Policy as follows:

Interview Online Department  
575 Broadway, 5th Floor.  
New York, NY 10012  
212.941.2800

 For the additional legal obligations that apply to your use of the Site, please see the Terms of Use.
